Contact

+917684071902 (Mobile) mohantyanshuman1994@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anshuman-mohanty-b50572a8 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service Microsoft Excel Leadership

Certifications

Developing Microsoft Azure and Web Services

Anshuman Mohanty

Senior Software Engineer at Infosys

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

Over the year i acquired a particular set of skills that are always be realistic to me .Working in development team i gain 4 years of experience in the vast world of Web development .I have worked with new technologies like ASP.NET MVC,WEB API,ANGULAR,JAVA-SCRIPT,J QUERY,SWAGGER and C# ,and as i am a full-stack developer i have SQL SERVER,MY SQL and ORACLE experience too.Currently i am learning REACTJS as it's trend in the market.Always trying to learn new technologies with the base-keeping legend one .

Experience

Infosys Senior Software Engineer January 2020 - Present (7 months) bangalore

Medtronic IT developer March 2019 - February 2020 (1 year) Bengaluru Area, India

IT develoepr

Espouse Technology Pvt.Ltd Web Developer August 2016 - March 2019 (2 years 8 months) Bangaluru,India

Education

Biju Patnaik University of Technology, Odisha Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng.), b.tech · (2013 - 2016) scte & vt(RIT)
diploma, Electrical Engineering · (2009 - 2012)

Activity

06/22/2020, Anshuman Mohanty added candidate to Senior Software Engineer